# **Zhao SongXun**

I am a full-stack developer with 7 years of experience.

I was hired by many clients and several startups including Producement, Live Bela LLC ,and Tranzport. At Producement company, I worked on several fintech projects and improved KPIs of projects.

I prefer working in an agile, fast-paced working environment remotely. because I believe autonomous, self-motivated and fast-paced working is critical for a developer's career.

With solid knowledge and experience in PHP, Node.js, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, I always strive to produce a fully tested and efficient code based on perfect OOP design and strict coding style.

Now, I am interested in CI/CD using Github & Gitlab pipeline to various cloud patlforms.

### I can provide:

- Full-time work for 5 days per week
- Suggest new ideas and apply the latest technologies
- Real-time communication
- Lead development

# EMPLOYMENT

#### 2020 - Present

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Producement

- + Work on various projects
- + Delivered Pactum Chatbot accepted by Walmart, raised 2 million USD
- + Work on PayQin
- + Salv Project demo.salv.com flexible rule management and good ui than its competitors

**Tech stacks:** Spring Boot, Java, Kotlin, Spock framework, Flutter **Website address:** www.producement.com

2018 - 2018

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Entybox

- + Fixed bugs and improved performance of legacy website
- + Implement new design and features using Django + Angular stack

**Tech stacks:** Python, Django, Angular, HTML5 Video, Video streaming

Website address: www.entvbox.com

2017 - 2018	<ul> <li>FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Live Bela LLC</li> <li>+ Launched Belacam photo sharing website using Python + Angular Stack</li> <li>+ Delivered performance-driven and user-friendly website with better UI/ UX design</li> <li>Tech stacks: Python, Django, Angular, Cryptocurrency, AWS Lambda</li> <li>Website Address: www.belacam.com</li> </ul>
2017 - 2017	NETWORK SECURITY ENGINEER - Moonrock Consulting + Utilized VSphere to run automation scripts + Launched firewall management website
2016 - 2017	BACKEND DEVELOPER - Tranzport LLC  + Developed API using Python + Django RESTful framework  + Delivered mobile application backed by API service
2016 - 2016	FRONTEND DEVELOPER - Play TAGG Limited + Developed new features and fixed UI/UX bugs + Implement new design
2015 - 2016	FRONTEND DEVELOPER - Spoilt Social TV  + Developed new features and fixed UI/UX bugs
EDUCATION	
2008 - 2014	BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE-Tianjin University of Technology  + Studied computer science, speech recognition, digital signal processing  + Submitted thesis for Noise reduction in speech
SKILLS	
	<ul> <li>Various languages and frameworks for web backend development.</li> <li>.NET/C#, Python/Django &amp; Flask, NodeJS/Koa, Loopback, MEAN, MERN stack, Mongoose, PHP/Laravel, Symphony,</li> <li>HTML, HTML5, CSS and various CSS architectures including SMACSS, BEM, OOCSS.</li> <li>Frontend MVC, MVVM, Component based frameworks</li> <li>Angular(any version), ReactJS, Nuxt, Vue.js, Next, Webpack, Babel, Javascript ES6</li> <li>Project Analysis</li> <li>Project Scheduling</li> <li>Test Automation</li> </ul>

- Infrastructure Design

# ACHIEVEMENTS

#### **SMOCKSY T-SHIRT WEBSITE**

https://smocksy.com

#### **BELACAM PHOTO SHARING WEBSITE**

https://belacam.com

## **TOPTENPERCENT COMPANY WEBSITE**

https://toptenpercent.com

# **JEWELRY SHOPPING WEBSITE**

https://thefutureofjewelry.com

## **CUBAN CIGARS WEBSITE**

https://finestcubancigars.com

## **PACTUM CHATBOT**

https://pactum.com

## **TULEVA PENSION WEBSITE**

https://www.tuleva.ee/en/

# **EXTERNAL LINKS**

LinkedIn <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/songxun-zhao-9394a574/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/songxun-zhao-9394a574/</a>

Github <a href="https://github.com/songxunzhao">https://github.com/songxunzhao</a>

Stackoverflow <a href="https://stackoverflow.com/users/6879870/songxunzhao">https://stackoverflow.com/users/6879870/songxunzhao</a>